<!-- produced for the bleb.org TV system at Thu Feb 2 08:39:01 2017 -->
<channel id="bbc1" source="XMLTV" date="02/02/2017">
	<programme>
		<end>0915</end>
		<title>Breakfast</title>
		<desc>
			The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast
			team. Also in HD. [S] Including regional news at 25 and 55 minutes
			past each hour.
		</desc>
		<start>0600</start>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>1000</end>
		<start>0915</start>
		<title>Rip Off Britain: Holidays</title>
		<desc>
			9/10. The team put airports and airlines under the spotlight. Also in HD.
			[S]
		</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>1100</end>
		<start>1000</start>
		<title>Homes Under the Hammer</title>
		<desc>
			Martin Roberts and Lucy Alexander visit a mid-terrace house in London, a
			detached house in Sevenoaks, Kent, and a bungalow in Stoke-on-Trent.
			Also in HD. [AD,S]
		</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>1145</end>
		<subtitle>Evans Family</subtitle>
		<desc>
			Families consider relocating down under. Will a week in Perth show Laura that
			Australia can give her the family time she is currently missing out
			on? Also in HD. [S]
		</desc>
		<title>Wanted Down Under</title>
		<start>1100</start>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>1215</end>
		<start>1145</start>
		<title>Caught Red Handed</title>
		<desc>
			4/20. Dom Littlewood looks at clever new methods to catch crooks
			red-handed. A man caught on camera stealing wedding dresses is about
			to have his big day ruined. Also in HD. [AD,S]
		</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>1300</end>
		<subtitle>Detling</subtitle>
		<title>Bargain Hunt</title>
		<desc>
			Antiques challenge. Tim Wonnacott and the team head to Kent County
			showground, with experts Jonathan Pratt and Kate Bliss. Tim also
			visits Charterhouse School in Surrey. Also in HD. [AD,S]
		</desc>
		<start>1215</start>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<start>1300</start>
		<desc>
			The latest national and international news stories from the BBC News
			team, followed by weather. Also in HD. [S]
		</desc>
		<title>BBC News at One</title>
		<end>1330</end>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<start>1330</start>
		<desc>
			The latest news, sport and weather from London. [S]
		</desc>
		<title>BBC London News</title>
		<end>1345</end>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<start>1345</start>
		<title>Doctors</title>
		<desc>
			Karen is mystified when she hears strange noises coming from Jimmi's
			consulting room. Bren causes tension between Ayesha and Tyler - can
			they weather the storm? Also in HD. [AD,S]
		</desc>
		<subtitle>New Leaf</subtitle>
		<end>1415</end>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>1500</end>
		<start>1415</start>
		<desc>
			9/10. The Sins of the Father: Period drama series. Father Brown
			investigates when the son of a local aeronautics magnate is murdered,
			while Lady Felicia loses her singing voice. Also in HD. [AD,S]
		</desc>
		<title>Father Brown</title>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<desc>
			4/10. Nicki Chapman visits the West Country to be reunited with couples
			she helped make the momentous step of moving from town to country.
			Also in HD. [S]
		</desc>
		<title>I Escaped to the Country</title>
		<start>1500</start>
		<end>1545</end>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<start>1545</start>
		<desc>
			9/15. Diplomatic Relations: Michael Buerk is joined by chef Paul Ainsworth
			to showcase food served at the grandest royal state banquets. Also in
			HD. [AD,S]
		</desc>
		<title>Royal Recipes</title>
		<end>1630</end>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<start>1630</start>
		<title>Antiques Road Trip</title>
		<desc>
			14/20. Antiques challenge. Charles Hanson and Mark Stacey start in
			Stratford-upon-Avon and end at their penultimate auction in
			Wotton-under-Edge. Also in HD. [S]
		</desc>
		<end>1715</end>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>1800</end>
		<title>Pointless</title>
		<desc>
			Quiz in which contestants try to score as few points as possible by
			plumbing the depths of their general knowledge to come up with the
			answers no-one else can think of. Also in HD. [S]
		</desc>
		<start>1715</start>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>1830</end>
		<title>BBC News at Six</title>
		<desc>
			The latest national and international news stories from the BBC News
			team, followed by weather. Also in HD. [S]
		</desc>
		<start>1800</start>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>1900</end>
		<start>1830</start>
		<title>BBC London News</title>
		<desc>
			The latest news, sport and weather from London. [S]
		</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>1930</end>
		<start>1900</start>
		<desc>
			If it's got Britain talking then it will get talked about on The One
			Show. Presented by Matt Baker and Angela Scanlon. Also in HD. [S]
		</desc>
		<title>The One Show</title>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<desc>
			Things go from bad to worse for one Walford family, and Babe stirs up more
			trouble for the Carters. Also in HD. [AD,S] Then BBC News.
		</desc>
		<title>EastEnders</title>
		<start>1930</start>
		<end>2000</end>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>2100</end>
		<desc>
			4/5. Mischief: Documentary. Animatronic spy creatures discover that
			mischief is rife in nature, but there are still rules that govern the
			animals' lives. Also in HD. [AD,S]
		</desc>
		<title>Spy in the Wild</title>
		<start>2000</start>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<start>2100</start>
		<title>Death in Paradise</title>
		<desc>
			5/8. Detective drama series set on a Caribbean island. A murder
			investigation propels the team to London in pursuit of their
			suspects. Also in HD. [AD,S]
		</desc>
		<end>2200</end>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<start>2200</start>
		<desc>
			The latest national and international news, with reports from BBC
			correspondents worldwide. Also in HD. [S]
		</desc>
		<title>BBC News at Ten</title>
		<end>2230</end>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>2245</end>
		<desc>
			The latest news, sport and weather from London. [S] Followed by national
			weather.
		</desc>
		<title>BBC London News</title>
		<start>2230</start>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>2345</end>
		<start>2245</start>
		<desc>
			David Dimbleby presents Question Time from Wallasey. On the panel are Sir
			Patrick McLoughlin, Rebecca Long Bailey, Maajid Nawaz, Nick Hewer and
			Laura Perrins. Also in HD. [S]
		</desc>
		<title>Question Time</title>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>0030</end>
		<start>2345</start>
		<title>This Week</title>
		<desc>
			Andrew Neil reviews the political week with Michael Portillo and guests.
			Also in HD. [S]
		</desc>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<desc>Detailed weather forecast. Also in HD. [S]</desc>
		<title>Weather for the Week Ahead</title>
		<start>0030</start>
		<end>0035</end>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<title>BBC News</title>
		<desc>
			BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news, with
			bulletins on the hour and the headlines every 15 minutes. Also in HD.
			[S]
		</desc>
		<start>0035</start>
		<end>0600</end>
	</programme>
	<programme>
		<end>0915</end>
		<start>0600</start>
		<title>Breakfast</title>
		<desc>
			The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast
			team. Also in HD. [S] Including regional news at 25 and 55 minutes
			past each hour.
		</desc>
	</programme>
</channel>